http://www.fascinations.net/policies/terms-of-service

Womens
Hosiery & BodystockingsShapewearGarters & Garter BeltsDancewear & FestivalBabydolls & ChemisesCorsets & BustiersTeddies & RompersBra & Lingerie SetsPantiesBedroom CostumesMensAccessories
PastiesJewelryShoesBridalWellness
Personal Care & Hygiene
Bath & BodyCosmeticsShavingFragrancesSafe Sex
Intimate CleansingToy CleanerCondomsSupplementsSex Toys
Vibrating
TraditionalAnal & PosteriorPanty VibeBullets & MinisCouplesClitoralInteractive App ToysRabbitsElectroG-SpotWandsStrap-OnsAnal
Anal BeadsButt PlugsVibratingKitsNon-Vibrating
Harnesses & Strap-OnsDildos & DongsGlass & MetalKegal & PC MuscleMale
Cock Rings - VibratingCock Rings - Non-VibratingPenis PumpsMale Masturbators Extenders & SleevesProstateChastitySoundsAccessories
Toy StorageWand AttachmentsBatteries & USBLubes & Stimulants
Stimulants
Clitoral & G-Spot Male EnhancersNipplesTighteningWarm & CoolOralLubricants
Anal PlayFlavoredPlant BasedOrganic & VeganSilicone BasedWater BasedHybridMassage
CandlesLotionsOilsToolsBDSM & Fetish
Restraints & CuffsCollars & GagsWhips & PaddlesNipple PlayElectroSensoryKitsSoundsFetish ApparelBlindfolds & MasksBody DecorParty, Games & Gifts
Gift CardsGift Baskets & Gift SetsRomance Games
Dice GameCouponsSexy KitsBoard GamesCard GamesParty GamesNovelties
CandyEdible WearNotes & CardsParty SuppliesPinsWearables (Sashes, Etc)Bachelorette/Girls Night
GamesDecorationEdiblesWearablesOtherBirthdayPrideBooks
Erotic FictionInstructionalNoveltyDVDsOn Sale
Sex Toys Party, Games & BooksLocations
Terms of service
Collecting and Sharing Personal Information:
FUNLOVE.COM comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. We explicitly ask when we need information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). For example, FUNLOVE.COM asks you for your name and e-mail address if you wish to join our mailing list, and we also may request that you provide Personal Information as part of a contest or promotion. We may also ask for other information from time to time, such as gender and date of birth, the disclosure of which will be optional. We use your Personal Information for various purposes consistent with US law, and we may occasionally inform you of new features, services, and products.
“Cookies”:
We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable the Site to relate your use of the Site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to the Site.
Disclosure of Information:
FUNLOVE.COM does not sell or rent individual user information to third parties. FUNLOVE.COM reserves the right to release current or past member information in the event FUNLOVE.COM believes that the membership is being or has been used in violation of the Terms of Service or other published guidelines or to commit unlawful acts, if the information is subpoenaed, or when FUNLOVE.COM deems it necessary or appropriate. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. By agreeing to the conditions of this Privacy Policy and FUNLOVE.COM Terms of Service, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when FUNLOVE.COM, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate.
Consent:
By using this website and the services available to you on our site, you consent to our collection and use of your information as described above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of our policies.
Links:
We may provide links to a number of other sites that we believe can offer you useful information and services. However, we are not responsible for the privacy policies of or any actions of any third parties that control the activities of such third party sites. We suggest contacting the relevant parties controlling these sites or accessing their online policies for the relevant information about their data collection.
General Information:
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, that information can be collected and used by others. Therefore, when you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and for any other personal information.
Your Account:
If you use this site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. FUNLOVE.COM does sell products for children, but it sells them to adults, who can purchase with a credit card. If you are under 18, you cannot access or order from FUNLOVE.COM. FUNLOVE.COM and its affiliates reserve the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in their sole discretion.
Models:
All models, actors, actresses and other persons that appear in any visual depiction of actual sexually explicit conduct appearing or otherwise contained in this Website were over the age of eighteen years at the time of the creation of such depictions.
Pricing and Content Information:
While FUNLOVE.COM strives to provide accurate pricing information, pricing, software or typographical errors may occur. FUNLOVE.COM cannot confirm the price of an item until after you order. In the event that an item is listed at an incorrect price due to an error in pricing, FUNLOVE.COM shall have the right, at FUNLOVE.COM’ sole discretion, to refuse or cancel any orders placed for that item. In the event that an item is mispriced, FUNLOVE.COM may, at FUNLOVE.COM’ discretion, either contact you for instructions or cancel your order and notify you of such cancellation.
Errors in pricing and availability of products will be corrected where discovered, and FUNLOVE.COM reserves the right to revoke any stated offer and to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions, including after an order has been submitted and whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is cancelled, FUNLOVE.COM will issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the charge. Bank policies will dictate when this amount is credited to your account.
FUNLOVE.COM employs various methods to provide you with values on our sites and in our stores. However, sometimes a price online does not match the price of the same item in our stores. In our effort to offer value pricing across several geographic regions, our store pricing will sometimes differ from online prices. Our stores do not honor Internet pricing, prices on FUNLOVE.COM.com or competitor advertisements from outside of a store’s local region.
General Disclosures
The FUNLOVE.COM website is operated by Marsoner, Inc. d.b.a. FUNLOVE.COM, on an “as is,” “as available” basis, without representations or warranties of any kind. To the full extent permitted by law, FUNLOVE.COM, Marsoner, Inc., and their affiliates (collectively, “FUNLOVE.COM”) disclaim any and all representations and warranties with respect to this site and its contents, whether express, implied, or statutory, including, but not limited to, warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular use or purpose.
Without limiting the foregoing, FUNLOVE.COM disclaims any and all warranties, express or implied, for any merchandise offered on this site or FUNLOVE.COM’ affiliate sites. This disclaimer does not apply to any product warranty offered by an item’s manufacturer. Please contact an item’s manufacturer for manufacturer’s warranty and policies.
FUNLOVE.COM, without limiting the foregoing, does not represent or warrant that the information on this website is accurate, complete, reliable, useful, timely or current or that this website will operate without interruption or error.
Further, FUNLOVE.COM, without limiting the foregoing, disclaims any liability as to the accuracy or completeness of each item description. Many product descriptions originate from the manufacturer of each item.
FUNLOVE.COM does not endorse nor make any warranties or representations about the options or other service or data you may access, download or use as a result of the use of the information contained on this website, or about any website you may access through this website. Links to other sites are provided for convenience only. Please make your own decisions regarding your interactions or communications with any other websi
Credit Card Processing & Chargebacks
In accordance with our credit card processing terms and conditions we will only allow chargebacks up to 180 days from the time of initial purchase
For credit card checkout (USAePay), billing address and the shipping address needs to be the same for us to process the order.
If billing and shipping address is different, customers should use PayPal to adjust the changes. Even if you do not have a PayPal account, you can still purchase using your credit card.
Free Delivery
On order $69+
Discreet & Secure
Shipping on all items
Customer Service
Support number (866) FUN LOVE
Customer Service
Visa, Mastercard, Amex, Paypal
Opens in a new window.
x
x
